Preliminary Inventory to the Saul Magnus Papers, 1918
Hoover Institution Archives
Saul Magnus Papers,
1918
30016
Magnus, Saul
1 manuscript box (0.4 linear feet)
Hoover Institution Archives Stanford, California 94305-6010
Military orders, memoranda, and maps, relating to activities of the U.S. 332d Infantry Regiment and the Italian 31st Division on the Italian front during World War I, October-November 1918. In English and Italian.
Administrative Information
Access
Collection open for research.
Access Points
Italy. Esercito. Divisione, 31.; United States. Army. Infantry Regiment, 332d.; World War, 1914-1918.; World War, 1914-1918--Campaigns--Italy.; Italy.; United States--Armed Forces.
Container List
- Italy. Esercito. 31 Divisione. Field orders, communications, memoranda, etc., 1918 October 11 - November 21 (Box 1.)
- Forces and services of the Austro-Hungarian army, 1918 May. Translated by the Intelligence Office of the 3rd Italian Army's Headquarters (27 pages, mimeographed)
- U.S. Army
  - A.E.F. General Headquarters
    - Program of training (first phase) for the 83rd Division, 1918 June 22 (34 pages, mimeographed)
    - Bulletin, 1918, Nos. 1-37; 1918 Jan 2-June 14
    - General orders, 1918, Nos. 1-97; 1918 January 1-June 17
  - A.E.F. 28th Infantry, France: Field orders, Nos. 60; 1918 May 22 (mimeographed)
  - A.E.F. 332nd Infantry, Italy)
    - Field orders, Nos. 1-10; 1918 October 28-November 23 (Carbon copies)
    - Field memoranda, 1918 October 29-November 17 (Carbon copies)
    - U.S. Army field messages, Nos. 1-28; 1918 October 29-November 14 (carbon copies)
    - War diary and daily situation report, 1918 October 29-November 18
- U.S. Legation, Italy. Office of the Military Attaché: Information bulletins, 1918 October 25-December 16 (carbon copies)
- U.S. War Department
  - Army regulations. Changes nos. 62-63, 1917
  - Chief of Staff - Lectures on staff work and staff duties in the British Army in France. Published with the permission of the British Military Mission, 1918 (89 pages, mimeographed)
  - Chief of Staff - Problem referring to mobilization and concentration of a division of the national army, 1917 (32 pages, mimeographed)
- Operations in Italy, 1918 (20 maps)